themobilestore.in 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Compare Mobile Prices India, Bobile Phones Best Deals India

Privacy Policy - Compare Mobile Prices India, Bobile Phones Best Deals India

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
  
|   |  |   PRIVACY POLICY  
---  
  
**Information We Collect**

At themobilestore.in, we are committed to providing excellent customer service and outstanding value in mobile phone and accessories while respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers. To better serve you, we may collect and maintain certain information regarding, your products and service preferences, date of special occasions related to people you buy gifts for (eg., birthdays), and billing and shipping information. Under no circumstances do we sell or rent this information to other businesses, and we protect and enforce the confidentiality of this information. We respect your privacy and seek to protect the trust you place in themobilestore.in. Our Privacy Policy is explained in more detail below:

**Security**

When you place an order online, your personal information and credit card information are encrypted using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet, making it virtually impossible for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred to themobilestore.in. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a database that is away from our Web site database so it isn't connected to the Internet, and is therefore safe from hackers. **Kindly keep a copy of your Proof of Identity, address and credit card at the time of delivery for verification.**

 ****Cookies**

To personalize your experience at both themobilestore.in we may use a feature on your Internet browser called a cookie. Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer and to retrieve certain information previously provided by you to us, so that you do not need to re-enter this information every time you shop at the site. Cookies also let us know how you found us (e.g., through a particular web site or advertisement). Cookies are not used to access information entered on the secure server. This information can only be accessed when you enter your name and password. If you choose to configure your browser to remove or reject themobilestore.in cookies, you will not be able to make purchases from the themobilestore.in site.

**Web Beacons**

In addition, from time to time we may contract with third party companies to help us better provide relevant products and services to you. Some of these companies use Web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs). A Web beacon is a transparent image that has been placed on a Web page and sends a signal when a user has visited that page. A Web beacon does not contain any personal information. 

**Internet Protocol**

For those individuals who visit our site but do not make a purchase, we collect and store IP ("Internet Protocol") addresses during the visit. No individualized information is collected, and the IP address is not traced to a particular individual. Similarly, we collect information, using that IP address, about the navigational or browsing activities of our visitors. Again, that information is not tied to any name or other personally identifying information but is used solely to provide generalized demographic data, such as what geographic areas our visitors are from and visitor browsing patterns. For those who make a purchase on themobilestore.in, in order to fulfill the order, we collect and store your name, address, shipping information, e-mail address, telephone number, purchase data, and billing information. 

**Use of Information Gathered**

We and the third parties who provide services related to themobilestore.in will use the information referenced above to fulfill your order and provide services related to themobilestore.in or the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, Web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. The third parties who provide any of these services are authorized to use this information only in connection with the services they are engaged to perform.   
In addition to using the information to fulfill your purchase order, we also retain some of that information in our customer database. We use that information to track your order, to respond to your inquiries and to make subsequent purchases you wish to make easier and faster. We also may use that information, from time to time, to contact you concerning our products, services, sales or special promotions of themobilestore.in or our corporate affiliates, including The MobileStore. We try to limit those contacts to ones that might be of interest to you. If you would prefer not to be contacted about our special offers, products or services, please notify us at the mailing address, e-mail address or phone number provided below: 

**The MobileStore Limited**  
Essar Techno Park, Bldg 'B',  
1st Floor, Pyramid Infotech Park,  
Swan Mill Compound, Near Kurla Bus Depot,  
LBS Marg, Kurla (W), Mumbai - 400 070.  
Phone : 6000 6363   
Email : mobicares@themobilestore.in

We currently send e-mails only to those themobilestore.in customers who are interested in receiving information about our products and services. If you have previously received such e-mails, but no longer want to, contact us by unsubscribing to an e-mail you receive from us or to the themobilestore.in Newsletter, as the case may be. Please be advised that since promotions may already be in process at the time of your request, it may take up to ten days before electronic contacts cease. As a result, you may receive mail or other solicitations from The MobileStore for a brief period of time after you make your request. You may also use the above addresses and phone number to correct or update any of the individual information we have stored. 

**Unsolicited E-mail (SPAM)**

Your privacy is very important to us. Be assured that, in accordance with our Privacy Policy, themobilestore.in does not sell or distribute our customer list to third parties. You should be aware, however, that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes 'harvest' your email address directly from your computer or another person's address book or even obtain your email address through programs that automatically search web pages and email traffic for email addresses. Please note that all email that originates from themobilestore.in will either display the themobilestore.in logo (HTML emails) or contain the themobilestore.in copyright notice (text emails). If you receive an unsolicited email that you believe is connected with themobilestore.in in any way, please forward the e-mail (as an enclosure) to [mobicares@themobilestore.in](mailto:mobicares@themobilestore.in?Subject:) and we will investigate. 

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of information by themobilestore.in and to the terms of this privacy policy. If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If we were to make a material change to our privacy policy, we will either post a notice on our Web site or send you an e-mail.

**Your Comments**

We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, feel free to drop us e-mail at [mobicares@themobilestore.in](mailto:mobicares@themobilestore.in?Subject:)

**  
|    
  
|   
---  
|
